[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following meals is the best source of fibers?", "correct_answer": "Arbys Market Fresh Ultimate BLT Wrap", "incorrect_answers": ["Subway Chicken Bacon Ranch Wrap (with cheese)", "Wendys Crispy Chicken Nuggets (5 pieces)", "Taco Bell Fiesta Taco Salad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the English translation of the name of the most famous book written by Nostradamus?", "correct_answer": "Centuries", "incorrect_answers": ["The Future", "Prophecies Gleaned from the Bible", "The Next Coming"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Rolling Stones member made a cameo appearance in the 2007 movie Pirates of the Caribbean: At Worlds End?", "correct_answer": "Keith Richards", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Watts", "Mick Jagger", "Bill Wyman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Angelina Jolie mostly teased about by her classmates when she was a student?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Her braces", "Her extremely thin body", "Her glasses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did Chicago Bears defensive lineman, William Fridge Perry, play college football?", "correct_answer": "Clemson", "incorrect_answers": ["South Carolina AT", "Georgia", "Eastern Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The blade or pyramid is a symbol used heavily throughout the movie The Da Vinci Code. Which of these does it NOT represent ?", "correct_answer": "Royalty", "incorrect_answers": ["Fire", "Masculinity", "The Christian Trinity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important role in Sleepless in Seattle did Ross Malinger play?", "correct_answer": "The male protagonists son", "incorrect_answers": ["The male protagonists boss", "The female protagonists son", "The female protagonists employee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1955, Ernest Borgnine starred in Marty, which earned him an Academy Award for Best Actor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Asian country is the Mount Unzen volcanic group located?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Vietnam", "China", "Thailand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the Earths first artificial satellite?", "correct_answer": "Sputnik 1", "incorrect_answers": ["Telstar 1", "Telos 1", "Explorer 1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular cartoon character is known for constantly wearing a Phrygian cap?", "correct_answer": "The Smurfs", "incorrect_answers": ["Teletubbies", "George Jetson", "Porky Pig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played James Bond in On Her Majestys Secret Service, showing the characters emotional side?", "correct_answer": "George Lazenby", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael York", "Sean Connery", "Roger Moore"]}]